Guided and directed by the Holy Spirit, Prophet T.B. Joshua ministers prayer to the people
who have come from all over the world in need of the saving power, in the name of Jesus Christ.
For satan's mission is to keep the children of God from the truth, where their true light comes from
and make them insensitive to God's voice.
As the man of God Prophet T.B. Joshua approaches this lady, every darkness in her life is exposed
and manifests, in Jesus' name.
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
I am the spirit of death.
I will kill her.
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
I entered her when she touched a dead body.
With just a wave of his hand, Prophet T.B. Joshua, through the power of the Holy Spirit,
delivers her, in Jesus' name.
Glory be to God.
Set Free In Jesus’ Name
TESTIMONY CONTINUES
Emmanuel!
(God With Us – Matthew 1:23)
Pastor Park Soon Gyu
South Korea
Praise the Lord!
Pastor Park Soon Gyu; I'm from South Korea.
Pastor Park Soon Gyu
South Korea
I have a ministry; I have been healing, delivering and blessing people for a long time.
Pastor Park Soon Gyu
Deliverance Testimony
We have heard from this sister; she says she is a pastor from Korea, that she is into ministry work,
that she heals and delivers people.
She came to The SCOAN because she had the spirit of fear.
Pastor Park Soon Gyu
Deliverance Testimony
She said one day she received sad news from the family of her friend,
that her friend had been brought down with a terrible disease of pancreatic cancer
and she had only that night to live; at the end of that day she would die.
She was asked to come and minister prayer to the friend.
Pastor Park Soon Gyu
Deliverance Testimony
As a prayer minister, she says she has about 30 people that form a prayer team
and she asked the prayer team, that they should go with her and pray for her sick friend.
Pastor Park Soon Gyu
Deliverance Testimony
She said ever before she made that move to go and pray for this sick friend together with her prayer team,
she heard a voice speaking to her that it would take the soul of that friend.
Pastor Park Soon Gyu
Deliverance Testimony
She said she made the move and went to the hospital.
By the time she got to the hospital, her friend was at the point of death.
Because her mouth was open, she could sense a bad breath coming from her,
like a decayed organ.
This was coming from inside her friend who was lying at the hospital at the point of death.
Pastor Park Soon Gyu
Deliverance Testimony
She said she was not happy with the state in which she met her friend at the hospital.
She spent one hour praying for her sick friend.
After that she went back home.
Pastor Park Soon Gyu
Deliverance Testimony
By the time she got back home, she later received the news from the hospital
that her friend had died that same night.
She went and took a shower.
Right in front of her house, there is a sensor-light.
If a human being is present in the front of the door, the sensor-light would be on.
Immediately you leave the spot where the sensor-light is located, it is supposed to go off.
She said that by the time she went into her house, showered and came back in front of her house,
she detected and noticed that the sensor-light was still on.
She shouted, "Who is there?", because she believed that somebody must have been there,
for the sensor-light to still be on.
She shouted, "Who is there?", but nobody answered her.
Pastor Park Soon Gyu
Deliverance Testimony
Since she had that experience, the spirit of fear entered her because she believed
that the spirit being which she could not see was following her.
It was that spirit being that was present in the front of the sensor-light that made that light to be blinking,
despite the fact that she could not see that being.
Pastor Park Soon Gyu
Deliverance Testimony
She said that after the death of her friend, one day she was brushing her teeth
and she was standing in the front of her mirror in her house.
Rather than seeing her own face in the mirror,
she saw the face of her dead friend, staring at her from inside the mirror.
And that evil spirit told her that it was going to kill her the same way it had killed her friend
with that sickness of pancreatic cancer and also stop her ministry.
Pastor Park Soon Gyu
Deliverance Testimony
She said that ever since that evil spirit entered her, anytime she stood on the pulpit to preach,
it was not her preaching, but that evil spirit in her preaching to the congregation.
Pastor Park Soon Gyu
Deliverance Testimony
She said that ever since this happened, her congregants would tell her,
"Pastor, anytime you are on the pulpit preaching, we see another spirit being moving
just at the spot where you are".
Pastor Park Soon Gyu
Deliverance Testimony
She said that because of the predicament she found herself in,
it caused sleepless nights and great discomfort to her.
She called the prayer team and asked them to pray for her, but despite the ceaseless prayers
she could find no solution to the problem she was having.
Pastor Park Soon Gyu
Deliverance Testimony
She said she used to watch Emmanuel TV right in Korea and she had seen what God had been using
Prophet T.B. Joshua to do in the lives of the people; to heal, to deliver and to bless people.
Not only that; she also witnessed the prophetic message that the man of God Prophet T.B. Joshua
gave many years ago that there would be a reconciliation between North and South Korea,
and she has seen that prophecy come to pass.
All this gave her a great conviction and belief that if she stepped her feet here, at The SCOAN,
God Almighty would deliver her.
Pastor Park Soon Gyu
Deliverance Testimony
She said ever since the evil spirit entered her, it caused disagreements between her and the husband,
she began to have marital problems and her husband got irritated by any little action she took.
She began to have negative thoughts towards her husband;
at some point she even wished her husband was dead.
Pastor Park Soon Gyu
Deliverance Testimony
She said that as she was seated in the church auditorium last Sunday, and the man of God
Prophet T.B. Joshua was preaching to the congregants that if you pray for somebody
without first delivering that person, that means you are inheriting the person's problem.
That person's problems would definitely come to you.
She said as she heard that message, she was shocked that the Prophet was talking exactly to her.
That was exactly the problem she was having and that was the reason why she was at The SCOAN that Sunday.
Pastor Park Soon Gyu
Deliverance Testimony
As Prophet T.B. Joshua was ministering prayer and deliverance to the congregants,
as he approached her, she wanted to run away but she could not.
She said she had gone to many churches, undergone many deliverances,
but she had never felt like that before.
Pastor Park Soon Gyu
Deliverance Testimony
She said that after the Prophet prayed for her; immediately he laid his hands on her,
that was all she could remember, until she found herself on the floor.
By the time she stood up, she felt so light.
Pastor Park Soon Gyu
Deliverance Testimony
Hallelujah!
She said ever since that prayer she has peace in her and she sleeps like a new-born baby.
Shall we put our hands together louder for Jesus!
How is she feeling now; is she still having those feelings of somebody following her anywhere she goes?
Pastor Park Soon Gyu
Deliverance Testimony
No, nobody is following me.
Hallelujah! Put your hands together once again for Jesus!
Pastor Park Soon Gyu
Deliverance Testimony
We have listened to that wonderful advice from our sister who said
that satan comes to kill, steal and destroy,
but our Lord and Saviour Jesus Christ has come to give life, and life in abundance.
She is advising everyone: That whatever problem or situation you might be facing, run to Jesus
and He will see you through, because He is the solution to all fundamental issues of life.
We give glory to God for the wonderful deliverance you have received, mum.
And we just want to advise you that as God Almighty has delivered you and set you free,
continue to walk in the light of your testimony, making God's Word the standard for your life
and we know that more and more blessings are still coming your way, in Jesus' name.
Once again, shall we put our hands together for Jesus!
TT ROBERT BEGIER 15/08/2018
RV: Mel Flowers 23/08/2018